Sync & corrections by Blue-Bird™
Improved by Fidel33
Modify by Blue-Bird™
Are you sure
you have the right keys?
Trust me,
it's the right key.
Okay, then, open the door.
It shouldn't be taking
so long, man.
20, 19, 18...
Rocky, those are very
slow seconds.
- Yo, kill that already.
- 17, 16...
- Dude, come on.
- 15, 14, 13...
- This is what I'm talking about.
- 12, 11, 10, 9...
I told you this was
gonna be fancy.
All right, so, just like last time.
No cash. The total take
has to fall below ten G's.
Yeah, yeah. Whatever,
Judge Judy.
- Come on.
- Let's do this.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Hey, Rocky, did you hear
that Kopecky's moving away?
Everybody's leaving.
You know, if we keep hitting
houses like today's...
Rocky, and...
Bye-bye, Detroit.
And hola, California.
Wait, wait.
You're going away, Rock?
Yeah, as soon as I can.
When are you,
when are you coming back?
Never.
You should come with us.
Uh...
What?
Everyone else is gone.
I got my dad here.
I'll miss you, then.
Dad?
You home?
Yo, this is it, man?
Minus my 40 percent.
Take it or leave it.
There's a fucking Rolex
in there, bro.
And what do you think...
I'm going to put it up
for auction at Sotheby's? Heh.
Do you know how much...
people on the street pay
for a hot Rolex?
- Heh.
- You want money?
Then steal money.
Fucking bullshit, bro.
Do you want
this new tip or not?
All right, let's hear it.
1837 Buena Vista Street.
House is with
your dad's security company.
I already checked.
Guy who owns it
is an Army vet loner.
No family.
Just him in the house.
That part of the city
is a ghost town.
It looks like a dump.
That's actually good news.
How's that good news?
The story goes...
some preppy girl
a few years ago...
ran over this guy's daughter.
- Jesus.
- The daughter dies...
and this preppy,
rich-ass family...
pays him off...
gives him a big-ass sediment.
Settlement.
Blow me, Your Honor.
All right, this guy
is sitting on at least...
300K.
Boom!
I mean, if I deliver
this stake to Raul, man...
he will shit his pants.
Do you think the money's
in the house?
I don't know.
Let's go find out.
Guys, no. We don't do cash.
Above ten K, it's major larceny.
That means ten years
if we get caught.
- We won't get caught.
- Okay, and then what?
That amount brings
a serious cop presence.
They'll do an investigation.
My dad could get in trouble.
I knew you'd bitch out, man.
I just knew it.
Alex, if we do this right,
we never have to do it again.
Where are you going?
We're not doing this one.
Seriously?
Give us the fucking keys, man.
- We'll fucking do it.
- Alex!
"Gulf War veteran reaches
six-figure settlement."
Six-figure settlement.
All right.
The suspect was leaving...
the rear entrance of the club.
Are you done, Diddy?
Be a doll and get your mother...
a large four-cheese from Tony's.
- So Trevor's living here now?
- Don't be a bitch, Roxanne.
It's just a few months
till he can find a new job.
You have no money in here.
You pay for it then.
I know you're making money.
I'm done.
Your lips look sore.
That's how you're making
your cash out there?
Ha, ha. Huh?
Okay, Diddy,
let's go for a walk.
I want to go to the beach.
Yeah, well,
it's not summer, monkeyhead.
I want to be a surfer.
There's no surf in Michigan.
- Not fair.
- Yeah, well...
some things
you can't change, baby.
No matter how unfair they are.
What a bummer.
Hey, you know
where there is surf?
California.
What do you say
you and I move there together?
Would you like that?
Okay.
I promise then.
Is that a new tattoo?
Yeah.
I got it last night.
- Is it a...?
- Ladybug.
Why a ladybug?
What?
When my dad left,
my mom started drinking...
and she told me that...
my dad's leaving was all my fault.
And I missed him a lot, so I'd cry.
She got so fed up with the crying...
that she would lock me
in the trunk of her car.
Sometimes for hours.
But there was this, um...
A little hole in the trunk...
and one time a ladybug flew in...
kept me company.
It made me feel safe.
When I reach California,
I'm gonna color this tat...
and that's the last time
I will mark my body.
If we get this money,
I'm going away with you guys.
I know you will.
At least four blocks around,
houses aren't occupied.
No people means
no Five-0 on patrol.
It's gonna be a piece of cake.
The guy's a shut-in...
hasn't left his house
in, like, five days.
I say we do it with him
in the house.
I'll get a chloro-bomb.
Oh, shit!
- Jesus.
- Fucking A.
Get off my fucking car, dog shit!
Shit, that's our guy.
Wait, is he blind?
He lost his sight
in Iraq or something.
That's kind of fucked up
to rob a blind guy, isn't it?
Just because he's blind don't mean
he's a fucking saint, bro.
We do this tonight.
The whole neighborhood
is fucking empty.
This guy's the last man standing.
The lights are out.
He must be asleep.
He's blind.
Lights off doesn't mean anything.
It's 2 a.m.
He's sleeping.
Let's take care
of that dog first, yeah?
Come on, man.
He's chewing it.
It'll be lights out in a sec.
There's four locks.
You got the other keys?
- I only have the one.
- Ah. Fuck me.
Why wouldn't he give backup
keys to the security company?
Because the money's in there...
and the paranoid fuck
doesn't trust nobody.
Let's check for a side door.
Sweet dreams, pup.
What's that?
We just have to point this
in the general direction...
of the master keypad,
and it'll kill the alarm.
Okay, open the fucking door, Dexter.
Yes. Got it.
Shit.
What's wrong?
It won't open.
This guy isn't messing around.
There's a bolt here.
I can feel it.
- Come on.
- That's too loud.
- Fucking stop.
What about that window?
There's no bars on it.
- I can fit in there.
- What?
No, we're not sending you
in there alone.
Nobody's sending me anywhere.
I'm going myself.
Help me up.
Here, Rocky.
You only got 30 seconds.
Okay.
Here. Come here.
Slow your roll, fool.
She must have got it by now.
She's fine.
Yeah, like you really give a fuck.
What'd you say?
That's my bitch in there.
Of course I give a fuck.
Let me give you some advice.
Be a good friend...
and stay in the fucking
friend zone, all right?
Are you okay?
Yes.
Shoes off.
- What the fuck?
- Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Okay.
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Yes, I'll be your valentine ♪
♪ Valentine, valentine ♪
♪ I love you ♪
Just three seeds, right?
Just three?
One, two...
and three.
Put three seeds in there...
and the cup is all empty.
Now you water it?
Okay, now we water it.
Okay, Mom.
Then it takes the water.
Just three seeds.
What are you doing?
Planting a tree.
How big is the tree
going to get?
As big as the sky!
Wow.
What does a tree need to grow?
Water, seeds, soil...
and sun.
Sounds good.
♪ Yes, I'll be your valentine ♪
♪ Valentine, valentine ♪
♪ I love you ♪
Then it will grow.
Mom, can I have more water?
Done!
What the fuck, dude?
The guy's gassed out.
He's out.
He's in Sleeping Beauty mode.
- It's fine.
- Guys.
That's a big-ass lock.
If the money's in the house...
probably in there.
You think you can
crack it open?
Yeah, I got this.
Fuck.
Jesus.
Do you have anything else?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I've got a more powerful tool.
What the hell is that?
It's a nine millimeter Beretta.
Gangster-style, bitches.
Why did you bring a gun?
This is a soldier's house, Alex.
Like I'm gonna come in here
without some chrome.
Money, you've never shot
a gun before.
Yeah, well, it's time
to pop that cherry, baby.
Because I'm going to pop that
shit like a fucking tuna can.
Do you have any idea
what bringing a gun...
to a burglary means?
Yeah, it gives me...
a better chance
to defend myself, Alex.
No, it means
you just gave this guy...
the legal right to shoot us.
Rocky, let's go.
No, no, no, no.
I think we should stay.
We have to leave.
This is not good.
You don't really think
just because...
you jerk off
to her Instagram selfies...
that makes you a Romeo?
Think again, bitch.
Fuck, I'm so out.
Alex.
Who's there?
Okay, man, just chill, all right?
Look, um...
I was wasted...
and I wandered in,
so that was my bad, all right?
So, I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna leave, okay?
Stay right fucking there.
Don't you fucking move.
Yeah, that's right.
I know what's in there,
and I ain't leaving without it.
You got me?
Now, you do as I say, all right?
Don't take one single step,
all right? Huh?
Well, do you hear me or what?
What, are you blind and deaf
all of a sudden?
Huh?
Motherfucker, I said stop.
I think you fucking heard me.
- Sorry.
- Don't you move.
What the fuck are you doing,
you old man?
I'll fucking shoot you.
Don't you fucking test me.
You're a fucking pussy.
What are you gonna do now,
huh? Huh?
You better fucking stop. Stop!
Don't make me
fucking kill you, man.
Please.
Please, just let me walk.
Let me walk.
Leave me alive.
Oh. Why would you do this?
What's the matter, please.
How many of you are there?
What?
How many?
It's just me, man...
all right? It's just fucking me.
Just let me go!
Please.
Please let me go.
Just let me go.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Okay, I swear to God...
Rocky, hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Maybe... Maybe we should...
call the cops before he does.
We'll come clean...
Wait.
What?
Oh, my God.
There's a lot more
than 300 grand in there.
That's got to be
about a million dollars.
Okay, let's get out of here.
The storm cellar door.
The door's bolted from the inside.
That could be our way out.
Let's go.
This way.
What?
Oh, shit.
The phone died.
Oh, fuck.
Hmm.
- Where's the door?
- I don't know.
Where is it? Do you see it?
Please help me! Please!
We need to get the fuck
out of here right now.
Come on. Let's go.
Look, the door's right here.
Look! Look at it!
Please!
What?
Rocky? Rocky.
Rocky, listen, listen.
Hey, that's our exit.
The door's right fucking there.
We can leave right now.
No, no, no, no!
She's the one
who killed his daughter.
We have to get her out of here.
No, no, no.
Rocky, we don't have time.
We'll... We'll get out of here,
and we'll call the cops...
and then they'll
come find her, all right?
The safe! The safe!
There's the safe!
The code from the safe upstairs.
- You remember it?
- Um...
2978, 78, 78, 2978.
2-9-7-8.
Oh...
Okay, got them.
He's coming.
- Hurry up.
- Okay, one more, one more.
Fuck, fuck!
I almost have it.
Almost... okay.
I don't care what you did.
I'll get you out of here.
Go, go, go!
- There's the door.
- There it is.
Are you okay?
Okay.
What's wrong?
It's locked.
You have the keys.
Don't you have the keys?
Fuck.
One of these should open it.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Oh, yes.
Come on.
He shot her.
No...
Oh.
No!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
My baby.
No!
We have to go back upstairs.
Yeah, listen.
Listen, okay?
These keys, they match
the locks on the front door.
All right?
If we get up there,
we can get out.
Okay?
Let's go now.
Shit.
Alex?
Rocky?
Please don't...
No, please...
Rocky?
Alex! Alex.
Rocky, Rocky.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
This way. This way, come on.
This way, come on, come on, come on.
Okay.
Oh, come on. Where am I?
Where is it?
Light. I see light!
Come on, come on.
Don't...
run.
Rocky...
go to the door.
Try the blue key.
- Do it.
- Okay.
Easy.
Easy, buddy.
Fuck.
- Rocky?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Easy, buddy.
Easy...
It's okay.
Okay, that's a good boy.
That's good.
All right.
That's...
That's good. That's good.
Oh. Fuck.
Rocky! Rocky.
Run, now. Go, go, go!
Upstairs, now. Go. Go, go!
Go! Hurry, hurry!
Go!
There's a door! Come on!
Let's go.
Hey, move this.
Come on.
Damn.
- Are those blocked up too?
- Yeah.
We're trapped in here.
Rocky, the remote.
Do you have it with you?
Come on. Okay.
- What are you doing?
- I'm pressing the panic button.
If I manage to get in range,
the system will call 911...
- and the police will come.
- No. Wait, we can't go to jail.
No. No, we won't. Okay?
This is robbery
versus kidnapping and murder.
The police won't care about us...
or why we were here
in the first place.
We would have helped them
get this guy.
But then we wouldn't
keep the money.
- We need to get out of this room.
- Up there.
Go!
Alex!
What are you doing? Go!
No! No, no!
Oh!
Hey!
Huh, huh!
Ah...
Ah.
Please, let me go.
Please, let me go!
I...
I understand you.
She killed your daughter.
You wanted her to pay.
I understand that.
I won't tell anyone.
You understand nothing.
Only a parent could know the...
bond between a father
and his child.
She should have
gone to prison, but...
rich girls don't go to jail.
None of this is going
to bring your daughter back.
That's not really true.
Cindy took my child
away from me.
I thought...
it's only fair...
that she give me a new one.
She was pregnant with my baby.
You killed them both.
- No.
- Well, they would be alive...
if you hadn't broken
into my home.
No.
You have to be held accountable.
Please.
Please, God.
God?
There's no God.
It's a joke.
It's a bad joke.
You tell me what God
would allow this.
What are you doing?
I'm not a rapist.
I never forced myself on her.
Stop.
I promised I would set her free...
just as soon
as she gave me a child.
But now she's gone.
But I'm done waiting.
Ah! No. No, no.
You can't do this to me.
There's nothing a man cannot do...
once he accepts the fact
that there is no God.
No!
No. No, no, no, no!
You're strong.
You're young.
You'll breed well.
No. Get away from me.
No! No!
No!
No...
Stop.
Shh, Shh, shh.
Nine months...
and I will give you
your life back.
Are you okay?
Rocky. Okay, yeah.
Rocky, did he...?
Did he hurt you?
Rocky?
You fucking bastard.
Fuck you!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, Rocky. Rocky.
Rocky. Rocky, it's over.
Come on.
How's that taste?
- Now what?
- Come on.
You're going to rot in prison
for what you've done.
Rocky, we can't
involve the cops now.
If we steal a million in cash...
and then lead the cops here,
he'll tell them about us.
Our blood is all over.
They'll get to us in a second.
You got what you came for.
Now take it.
Get out of my house!
Look, he's buying our silence.
He needs us to take the money.
It's one or the other.
Whatever you choose,
I'm with you.
- Okay.
- This one.
Let's get out of here.
I need to find the key.
All right.
That key won't...
I got it.
You're worthless out here.
Fuck.
Shit!
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Ah, fuck!
I'm sorry, Alex.
I'm so sorry.
No!
Don't!
Ah, no...
No. Ah...
Ah! Don't...
No.
What is that?
You and me at the beach.
Train service to Los Angeles...
will be boarding shortly
on platform six.
This house behind me
on Buena Vista...
belongs to a retired Army vet...
who fought
for our country in Iraq...
and lost his sight as a result
of a grenade splinter.
Last night, two burglars
broke into his home...
and attempted to rob
and brutally attack him.
This visually impaired man
was able to defend himself...
shooting and killing
both his attackers on the spot.
Now, the man did
sustain some injuries...
but doctors say he is
in stable condition.
He'll be released
from the hospital soon...
and able to return to his home.
No goods were reported stolen
by the victim.
I'm Dayna Clark, WADL News.
Improved by Fidel33
Modify by Blue-Bird™
Sync & corrections by Blue-Bird™